okay so here go felicity huffman who says i felt like i had to give my daughter a chance at a
future and so it was sort of like my daughter's future which meant i had to break the law
because felicity huffman is one of the people who paid to do some slick shit to get their child
into an ivy so she couldn't go to juco your daughter who wasn't doing what she needed to
be doing the whole time that she was in school which is why she wasn't getting into the schools
that she wanted to so instead of teaching your daughter to be held accountable for her actions
by having her go to a junior college for a couple years until she gets her grades up so then she can
go to where she wants to go you instead taught her that with money you don't have to do that you can
just jump the line and yet people want to make noise about affirmative action
ma'am please quit trying to make this about you were doing what you needed to do for your child
and this is more about you feeling like you could just do whatever you wanted for your child
because you're white